a very strong move has already happened
into stocks like Pro ICICI life ICI
General Insurance HDFC life all of them
at Record highest this GST council
meeting to be held today uh may cut the
GST which is 18% on insurance costs down
to maybe 5% how do you view this
potential development and any favorites
here yeah I would say that definitely
we've seen some very uh good Traction in
the in the insurance space uh it's BFC
life has been a distinct performer out
there it it did consolidate and then
again moved moved higher and also if you
look at the other some of the other
insurance companies like IC if I look at
IC
Lombard General that is is comparatively
far stronger as compared to HDFC
live so I would say that currently it's
trading at record high so if you look at
last week the stock was up by almost 5
6% and uh uh if you if you look at the
stock the stock isn't showing any signs
of pullback but this is one can keep a
close watch see you have to understand
that from a long-term perspective these
are these are companies where one can
definitely invest and build a portfolio
but one need not be only in the
insurance space so a couple of stocks
like I say say Lombard could be one of
them or LC could be so you have a PSU
and a private private player and then
but you have to average it out in case
the market does correct is trading at
record highs but this is one stock which
continues to defy I would say all laws
of gravity and continues its upper Trend
because the stock uh on 4th of June the
election results day was trading around,
1400 1480 currently it's around 2200 so
despite the market correction the stock
has not corrected so that c tells me
that there's definitely a lot of smart
money which is invested in the stock and
they're not letting it
n
[Music]